Contact

7707150917 (Mobile)

www.linkedin.com/in/william-joey-stout-9348787b (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Experienced Trainer
Cerner Software
Patient Advocacy

Certifications
CCRN

William "Joey" Stout

Emory Saint Joseph's

Suwanee, Georgia

Summary

Increasing quality outcomes for patients through collaboration, technology, and innovative process improvements

Qualified Critical Care RN with unique combination of experience in clinical nursing, technology, training, and industrial engineering. Uses knowledge, theory, research and experience to respond to changes in clinical situations and to personalize care for patients and families. Maintains standard of care through sound understanding of the critical care population. Proven experience collaborating to improve clinical systems, leading teams, and providing training and support to hospital staff during system implementation. Serves as a resource to colleagues.

SUMMARY EXPERIENCE

- 9 years Nursing in hospital environment on cardiac and critical care units.
- 1 year Business Intelligence software training, installation, and report writing.
- 3 years Developing and implementing training for software and technology.
- 9 years Industrial Engineering and process improvement.

Competencies That Accelerate Results

- Clinical Reasoning
- Patient and Family relationship management
- Customer Focus
- Learning Facilitator
- Collaborates
- Resolves Conflict
- Process Improvement
- · Managing through influence
- Ethical Decision Making
- Responds to Diversity

Experience

Emory Healthcare eICU Clinician January 2015 - Present (5 years 7 months)

WellStar Health System
Critical Care Registered Nurse
January 2011 - Present (9 years 7 months)
Roswell, Georgia

Northside Hospital Registered Nurse Medical/Cardiac Unit July 2010 - January 2011 (7 months) Cumming, Georgia

Northeast Georgia Medical Center Registered Nurse Cadiac Stepdown Unit November 2008 - October 2010 (2 years) Gainesville, Georgia

Hunter Douglas Manager of Quality Control January 2003 - January 2004 (1 year 1 month) Norcross, Georgia

Gwinnett Technical College Adjunct Instructor September 2002 - December 2002 (4 months) Lawrenceville, Georgia

Java instructor

Digiquant
Consultant/Trainer
August 2000 - August 2001 (1 year 1 month)

Computer Associates, Inc.
Consultant/Trainer
March 1999 - August 2000 (1 year 6 months)
Atlanta, Georgia

Hunter Douglas Process Engineer April 1998 - March 1999 (1 year) Norcross, Georgia

American Candy Company Industrial Engineer March 1995 - April 1998 (3 years 2 months) Selma, Alabama

National Vision Associates Industrial Engineer January 1994 - March 1995 (1 year 3 months) Lawrenceville, Georgia

Support System Associates, Inc.
Industrial Engineer/Team Lead
January 1991 - January 1994 (3 years 1 month)
Warner Robins, Georgia

Education

Georgia State University

Bachelor's degree, Registered Nurse · (2004 - 2008)

Georgia Institute of Technology
Bachelor's degree, Industrial Engineering · (1987 - 1990)

Bluefield State College
Associate's degree, Pre-Engineering · (1985 - 1987)